You really can't help flirting
with my husband, huh?
I get it! You're rich and pretty!
But you're so insecure!
Ana hired me to be a loyalty tester.
To find out if you're having an affair.
That was unnecessary, Ana.
There are just so many things
about you that I don't get.
And all of this happened
just because of loyalty testing.
Are you seriously
blaming Ana for getting upset
when you flirted with her husband?
I don't care!
I love Ben.
Are you finally awake?
You can reach all you want,
but you will never ever touch what's mine.
Please help me.
I'm begging you.
Congratulations, Attorney!
I mean... sorry, Mr. CEO.
Wow!
What are you doing here?
Ben, I'm here to talk to you.
Ben, where are you?
You said you would be right back.
Hello, love.
I'm sorry I didn't update you right away.
I had to attend to an emergency.
Okay, well...
Just... come back when you can.
Yeah, I'll let you know.
I love you. Bye.
Okay, bye.
What happened to that, Ging?
That wasn't me.
Ging, what happened to this?
It wasn't me.
How could I do that? I was tied up.
Who did it, then?
There was a woman.
A woman?
There was a woman
who wanted to help me.
At least someone cares about me.
A woman came here and broke that window?
Yes. There was a woman there
before you arrived.
Ging.
Are you telling the truth?
What did she look like?
What did she look like, Ging?
There was a woman there
before you arrived.
Stay here, okay?
Ging, don't go anywhere.
That woman you slapped at the café...
is it the same woman
who caused a scene at my house?
How do you--
Ana, people are talking.
So, am I right?
-
Am I right?
She's Mariano's physical therapist.
And now, she's your husband's
physical therapist too.
Yes.
But Ma, you don't need
to know these things.
Ben and I are okay now.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
You know what I'm curious about?
How did she end up being a homewrecker?
Why? What for?
What do you mean, why?
I'll say it again, Ana.
People are talking.
Everyone's already talking
about what happened at the café.
What if they find out
about the scene at my house?
They won't find out.
Ana, that woman
walked out of my house unscathed.
You and your husband
did nothing about it.
I'm sure that woman will keep coming back
to cause a scene.
And I will deal with her every time.
But please, Ma...
please stay out of it, okay?
You take care.
I'll call someone to fix the window.
Regina will never admit that she broke it.
These past few days,
she's been making up a lot of stories.
How did you get to my office?
I found a way.
You weren't answering my calls.
Don't ever do that again.
Ben, I wouldn't have had to do that
if you had answered my calls.
I'm leaving.
Hey, Ben, hold on.
You're leaving Regina again?
You leave whenever she's calm.
And you're never here when she needs you.
Mara.
I can't stay here long
because I have a life of my own.
And I don't?
You have a job.
Your job is to take care of my sister.
Or is something else keeping you busy?
Hmm?
What do you mean?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Just say it to my face, Ben.
What are you implying?
Do you smoke, Mara?
Okay.
Yes. What's wrong with that?
You didn't even tell me.
And...
if you could hide something
that's not a big deal,
you're probably hiding
something even bigger.
You're scared of your own shadow.
Watch over my sister.
I'm paying you to do your job.
All you care about is money, huh?
So, what is it you want, Mara?
I'm getting tired, Ben.
There'll come a day
when your money won't be enough
for everything I'm doing.
What exactly is your plan here?
Do you even have a plan?
Is your plan
to just lock up your sister forever?
Mara, there are things
you don't understand.
My sister will be part of my life
at the right time.
- Ben.
- Take care of my sister.
It's your sister
we're talking about here, Ben!
I'm so annoyed with Brian.
He didn't want to let me go.
He has a lot of problems in...
his personal life.
He no longer does his job
at the firm properly.
I'm sorry I had to go,
and I couldn't come back.
So, what happened?
People are talking about me, Ben.
About what happened to Beth and me...
in the café.
Yeah, I heard them.
You heard them?
The people gossiping about it.
And then?
What did you do?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
What did you do?
You didn't do anything?
Is it because you agree with them
that I'm in the wrong?
She attacked me.
She slapped me first.
I am the victim.
Ben! I am your wife.
I know that, Ana.
And I'm on your side.
It's just that... that was a work event.
How could I argue with the people there?
We better go to sleep.
Ana...
We need to be early tomorrow.
We'll have breakfast with Mom.
Benjamin deserves that award.
I even wonder why they just gave it now.
He has done so much for the azucarera
and for the people here in Vallente.
It sounds like you want Attorney Ben
to run in the next election.
Ladies,
let's not get ahead of ourselves, okay?
Oh! Speaking of.
- Ana! Hello.
- Hi, Ma.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hi, Ben!
Mom, I didn't know you had a meeting.
You could've just called me
to say what you had to say.
Ugh, don't be silly.
This is why I asked you to come here.
- Is this for us?
- Yes.
Nanny, put it in the kitchen.
Thank you so much.
Attorney Ben will be awarded
as this year's Child of Visayas.
It is to acknowledge
your work and dedication to our community.
Congratulations.
Are you sure?
- Wow.
- Ben.
Do you think we joke about this thing?
The Child of Visayas
is a very prestigious award.
Yes, of course we're sure.
You'll need
to prepare a speech for the ceremony.
You wouldn't reject Vallente, would you?
Of course not.
Uh, thank you.
I will have this arranged
with my secretary.
- Perfect!
- Thank you.
Benjamin, I am so proud of you.
Congratulations to both of you.
I'm so happy!
Nanny,
please keep this for Mom.
And then, you can serve this
to those she's meeting with.
All right, keep that.
I'll handle this myself.
Ana, dear.
I wanted to...
congratulate you and Ben for your award.
You should say that to him instead.
I know I've told you that...
you shouldn't put up with your husband.
I was wrong.
I've realized you're a wife
who won't easily lose
your love for your husband.
That's why that award is for both of you.
I know Ben wouldn't do
what people said he did...
if you hadn't supported him
in everything he does.
That's why Ben is very lucky to have you.
Thank you.
Dad.
My child, may I hug you
just for a moment?
Ben and I are heading out now.
We still have work to do.
Take care, dear, okay?
Go, why not?
You're not new
to fashion fundraisers, right?
Yeah, but after everything
that's happening, I...
I don't know, but I just want
to keep a low profile for now.
It's not surprising
that Attorney Ben has a mistress.
He's handsome and smart.
A lot of people will want him.
Maybe Ana isn't looking after him well.
Why can't she look after him
when they don't even have kids?
It's just the two of them, right?
Perhaps it's Attorney
who is taking care of Ana.
Her family has a history
of mental health issues, right?
So, maybe Attorney
really has gotten tired of her.
That's why he looked for someone else.
- Kat, Kat! No, Kat!
- What the hell?
- No! Kat...
What-- They are talking nonsense!
Kat, no, it's not worth it. Stop.
We should have said something
to put an end
to people gossiping about you.
Ana?
I can't help it.
I don't want
to be affected anymore, but...
I can't stop myself.
So, you need to do something about it.
And what? Argue with them?
No.
You need to redeem yourself.
Why?
Why would I have to redeem myself
if I didn't do anything wrong?
I know, and I agree with you.
But not everyone thinks the same way.
In their eyes, you are in the wrong.
Hands?
So, I said yes to a fundraiser.
- Yeah?
- For Vallente Orphanage.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
They're going to exhibit my designs.
Wow, that's great!
Wow, so more people
are gonna see your work.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm so happy to hear that.
Good job.
- Thank you.
- I'm proud of you.
- Okay.
- Thank you so much.
Ana, Attorney, they're here.
- Okay, Nanny.
- Thank you, Nanny.
- Okay? Thank you very much. Let's go.
- Yes.
Bridge, let's just talk later.
Wait, why are you so hard to contact?
What "important thing"
are you doing now, Beth?
I said let's just talk later.
Hey, Beth!
I worked a lot of jobs
in Recto back then.
Um...
I worked as a porter.
I sold an assortment of stuff.
I worked as a pedicab driver.
Until eventually,
I had the chance to be a...
service crew at a small restaurant.
So, my salary increased then.
That was when I was starting college.
I can't seem to imagine
you doing those jobs, Attorney.
We knew you in Vallente
as Attorney Ben already.
And now, the Child of Visayas awardee.
Oh, that's true.
I went through a lot
before I became a lawyer.
Good times, tough times.
But thanks to my...
very beautiful and loving wife...
and everyone who supported me, I'm here.
Even though you're from Recto,
the people you really helped
are those here in Vallente.
People think that...
I have a foundation.
Um...
But you know...
The azucarera and I,
we try to help others from outside.
But we know, Attorney,
not all are your fans.
You said you're an open book.
Rumor has it
that you and your wife
are having problems.
Oh, my God.
No, that's not true.
So, there's no third party?
"Third party"?
- Yes.
- Third party.
No, that's not true.
There's no third party.
Um...
My wife and I,
we're very okay,
because if we weren't,
my barong would've been a mess today.
She prepared this barong for me.
But I'll tell you something,
you know...
We're a normal married couple.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
We argue,
but we always talk things through.
Mm.
But to say we're drifting apart,
or that there's a "third party,"
or that I don't love my wife anymore?
That will never happen.
Well, straight from Attorney Ben himself.
It couldn't be any clearer.
So, we want to know more
about your bagasse project...
It was nice having you over.
Yes, thank you for having me.
And thank you for the delicious snacks.
Oh, my gosh, it's nothing.
- I'm glad you liked it.
- Thank you.
Are you sure we covered everything?
- Yes, definitely, Attorney.
- Okay.
- Thank you so much.
- All right, see you soon!
- See you! I'll go ahead.
- Thank you, thank you.
- All right.
- Bye.
Hey.
That was a lot.
You did well.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Tired?
- Get some rest.
- Okay.
Ben!
Oh. Hello!
Brian.
Ben.
I hope you don't mind my sudden visit.
No, of course not.
- Of course not.
- Mm-hmm.
- What's up?
- Ana.
- Good to see you again.
- Hello.
Yeah, we met at the party.
- Thank you again. And...
- Yes.
I heard you were together at the launch?
Yeah.
- How are you?
- Uh...
I heard you're going through something.
Yeah.
Ah, yes. Yeah...
Actually, I am going through something
right now.
Thanks for asking.
Anyway, uh...
Ana, would it be okay if I borrowed
your husband for a quick minute?
I just need to talk to him
about something.
Oh, okay, okay.
So, um...
I'll leave you two alone.
- Okay.
Brian, sorry I never got back to you
the other day.
You were saying you're short?
Mr. CEO,
you've been up to something
behind your wife's back again,
haven't you? Tsk, tsk.
- What?
- You.
You've been using me
as your excuse with your wife.
That means
there's something
she isn't supposed to know.
Am I right?
Okay.
All right, Brian. How much do you need?
I was going to ask for one million.
But I changed my mind.
Three million.
What?
I'm asking you for three million, Mr. CEO.
- Yeah?
- You're serious?
You show up at my house
to borrow money? No, I'm sorry.
You're asking me for three million?
It's this simple, Ben.
Three million for my silence.
Because...
I know things, Ben.
You know things?
Things that could bring you down, Mr. CEO.
I know everything.
Everything!
Maybe you've forgotten...
we move in the same circles.
One post from me on social media,
and the news will spread fast.
People will start asking questions.
Oh, my God.
Especially in this town of Vallente,
where everyone thinks so highly of you.
Fine.
Three million.
Of course you'll give it to me.
Of course.
What's three million
compared to the life
you're trying to protect, Mr. CEO?
But I can't give it to you
right now, okay?
I'll fix it.
I'll call you.
Okay. I'll take your word for it.
I'll wait for your call, Mr. Big Shot.
Thank you.
Hey.
Thanks for helping me with the interview.
Thank you.
You didn't have to
put the spotlight on me earlier.
No, I want to.
And I wouldn't be here
if it weren't for you.
Everything I do is for you, Ana.
Good night.
Okay, good night.
Hey.
I hope you have a good sleep tonight.
Ben, do you have my money?
Oh, there's nothing there.
I was gonna offer you my yacht.
- No.
- Would you like a yacht?
You want to see it?
It's not far from here.
It's really nice.
Ben, do you or do you not have my money?
Hand it over!
Okay.
I don't have it.
What?
The money's not here,
it's on the yacht.
Brian, do you expect me
to bring three million pesos with me?
Ben, do you understand me?
I don't want your goddamn yacht!
- Give me my money. Give me the money.
- It's on the yacht.
Brian, you're not listening.
The money is on the yacht.
Ben, no matter how hard
you push your yacht down my throat,
you won't convince me.
Just give me my money.
Give me my three million pesos.
Brian, listen.
The money isn't here,
it's on the yacht.
What? Ben, are you deaf or dumb?
I don't want your yacht!
I am not going to your goddamn yacht!
Give me my three million.
Brian, I told you,
the money is on the yacht.
I don't have it with me.
Ben-- Let me remind you.
Are you going to give me the money,
or do you want me to tell everyone I know
about your secrets?
Brian,
I really don't have the money here.
- No, no, no.
- It's on the yacht.
Just answer the fucking question.
Of course I'll give you your money.
It's on the yacht!
Let's go!
You're really pushing my buttons, huh?
Fine. You'll regret this.
No, no, no, Brian, Brian.
Please, please, please don't.
You bastard!
Damn it-- Ben!
I said let me go!
You?
Please let me go, ma'am.
This is kidnapping--
If Ben finds out--
Go ahead.
Keep talking.
I'll make your cheeks swell up like hell.
Now leave my daughter's husband alone.
You have no idea
how crazy I can get for my daughter.
Yes.
I am doing this for my daughter.
Because I don't want her life
to be ruined.
I'm not the one who's destroying her life.
You know, no matter what you say,
you are still a homewrecker.
I know your kind.
Because I once made
the mistake of begging for my husband.
But what did you do?
You ruined me!
Too bad for you.
You'll be punished
for all the things others did to me.
I have so much time in my hands.
And I have a lot of things in my mind
that I can do to you.
Your family will be blamed
if I disappear--
That mouth of yours is so annoying!
You know what?
Even if I let you go,
you know what'll happen, right?
You're a physical therapist, aren't you?
So you know what'll happen
if your bones break.
For the last time,
stay away from my daughter's husband.
Do you understand?
If you don't,
I will do much worse things to you.
Do I make myself clear?
Answer me!
I know.
You bitch!
Oh, my goodness...
Let's go.
I am warning you, Beth.
I can do unexplainable, crazy things
for my daughter's love.
The heck?
What is this mess? Nanny!
Clean up this mess! Oh, my God!
What's this?
Dinner... for you.
The staff helped.
But I cooked everything.
What stupidity is this?
It's just for tonight.
This is all for you.
Look, Reynaldo.
If I wanted a candlelit dinner,
I would've told the staff.
And besides,
why would I want to share
this kind of dinner with you?
It's too late for this kind of nonsense!
Happy anniversary, ma'am!
Anniversary?
- I'm going, Ben.
- Huh?
- I don't--
- Where are you going?
Hey, sit down.
- Ben...
- Sit down, Brian.
- Come-- Brian, Brian, Brian.
- Let me go!
Brian, Brian.
It's okay. It's okay.
- Let go of me!
- It's okay.
I said it's okay.
Fuck.
Look what you did.
Now I have to clean this mess.
- Huh?
- Please stop...
What?
What are you saying?
You want me to stop?
Is that what you said?
Well, damn you.
"Stop." Exactly.
I've been asking you to do that.
I've asked you to stop.
I didn't want to do this, either.
That's why I'm here in Vallente, aren't I?
Simply because I want to live in peace.
But here you are, you damn bastard.
You all want to destroy
the things I've worked hard on.
I just want to live a quiet life
with my wife, okay?
I'm doing my job quietly.
What were you planning to do?
People like you are the ones
who make me do this.
You're asking me
for three million pesos, huh?
Did you think I'd just give it to you?
You thought you'd get it easily?
Then you're damn wrong.
Fuck!
Brian?
Brian.
Fuck!
Ma'am Imelda!
Ma'am Imelda! Ma'am Imelda!
- Oh, my goodness!
- Ma'am Imelda!
I'm going to teach this kid a lesson.
- Wait!
What is it? You're so loud!
What do you have to say
that you had to wake me up?
Speak now!
Papa is gone.
Miss Cedes?
- Where's the coffee?
- Here, sir.
Hand it here. Okay. I got it.
- Thank you.
Good morning.
Morning.
Did you sleep well?
- Mm-hmm.
- Good.
I'm so happy.
- Please, sit down.
- Yeah.
Ah, Ana...
You should keep doing that.
Let your mind rest at night.
To help you sleep well.
Anyway,
please enjoy your runny eggs
and soft bacon.
Thank you.
Hello, Ma?
Wha-what? What do you mean?
Are you sure
the flowers are already in the chapel?
Yes, ma'am.
- What about the coffin?
- It's there.
- Ma...
- Are you sure? Okay.
- Make sure to check everything.
- Okay, ma'am.
Ma, it's okay.
What's happening?
You know what's happening.
I'm organizing
your father's burial, what else?
- Ma...
- Would you like us to help?
No need, Benjamin.
I can do it on my own.
But if you want to help,
fine, suit yourself.
If you changed your mind,
you can just relax.
Wait. Hey, come here.
Where's the catering?
What happened to the catering?
What time are they arriving?
They can't be late.
- We can't serve spoiled food.
- Ma.
It's embarrassing to the guests.
- What?
Slow down.
Where is Juancho?
Juancho is in the morgue.
He's taking care of your father.
- Hey! Come here.
- Yes, ma'am?
- What are you still doing here?
- What is it?
I told you to bring Reynaldo's clothes.
Why are you still here?
I already did, ma'am.
- Ma?
- Options.
Give them options.
- Hurry up! I still have a lot--
- Ma.
Can you just...
Ana, look.
I am so busy, okay?
I have so much to take care of!
You know,
I want this wake to be fabulous.
I'm sure a lot of people will come.
If you want to help, then help.
If you don't want to,
take a seat, relax,
or do whatever you want!
You! We should bring
the expensive glasses to the chapel,
so they would look nice.
It's okay.
She's not okay.
Maybe it's her way of... coping.
It's okay. Just let her.
You should relax.
I'm sorry for your loss, Imelda.
Thank you.
You're so lucky, Imelda.
Even though Ana's husband is a CEO,
he's still helping out here.
That's how much Ben loves my daughter.
Ma'am, Madam Mona is here.
Thank you.
Excuse me for a second.
Imelda.
Our deepest condolences.
- Thank you.
We appreciate it.
Last time...
we were the ones
offering you our condolences.
Imelda, we should stop meeting
in this kind of setting.
I know.
I'm glad
your granddaughter could join you.
Surprisingly,
she agreed to come.
Come here.
Do you want anything?
- Do you want some drinks?
- No, thank you.
I'll pay my respects first.
- I'll accompany you.
- Ana, come with her.
I'll only let you talk
to her granddaughter this time.
Do you understand?
- Get on with it.
- Thank you.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Let me handle this.
Ana said you haven't eaten yet.
There's food in the room.
Come on.
Thank you.
Please put it there.
That's his son from another woman.
I can't believe Imelda. She accepted him?
She even prepared a beautiful wake
for the man
who had cheated on her.
Do you know the cause of death?
It's probably because of stress
from what Ana did to Ben's mistress.
Who wouldn't be stressed out by that?
Especially when he learned
that his daughter connived
with some woman to flirt with her husband.
Hello.
Do you believe in ghosts?
Could you let me know
when the spirit of Ana's father
pays you a visit
because you keep on badmouthing her?
But...
please, just for your clarity,
let me say it myself, okay?
The truth is...
my wife didn't do anything wrong.
And secondly...
there's no other woman in my life...
but...
my loving wife.
- Are you okay?
- Thank you.
I hate you so much.
I hate you.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
Why am I crying?
Oh, my gosh.
I want to go home, Juancho! Let's go!
Let's go! Hurry up!
Let's go.
I can't stand it here.
I thought I hated him too.
Why does it hurt?
Maybe you didn't hate him.
You just hated the things he did.
Ging.
It's good.
How did you get here?
Ging.
- Hi. Good morning.
Ben.
Good morning. Where were you?
I did a morning walk. It starts outside.
Let everyone enter!
We all admire
the Child of Visayas.
- Attorney Benjamin Santos!
Do you want to eat?
Yes.
My brother killed my husband.
- Regina.
Did you see it?
-
It's better to have a gun than a knife.